Yep, just like that. Perfect.
Sweet.
Very exciting for me, very exciting for
my family. You know, last year just
coming in and
just being a Viking
kind of a dream come true, so to speak.
So, to to get to do it again and run it
back with a great locker room, great
coaching staff and just really a really
well-run organization
means a lot and and I'm pretty spoiled
by it. So, [music]
I'm pretty blessed to be back.
Yeah, I think every year I'm most
excited about just building those
relationships in the locker room. You
know, it's there's going to be a lot of
familiarity in there, but there's always
new faces and every year it's its own
team and so building that bond, building
those relationships
and for me getting to do it the entire
off-season, [music]
that'll mean a lot to me and I'm excited
for that.